<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>John Cummings's Portfolio on Home</title><link>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in John Cummings's Portfolio on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jcummingsutk.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Diabetes Classifier</title><link>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/diabetes_classifier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/diabetes_classifier/</guid><description>Goal: The goal of this project is to develop a good conservative diabetes classifier. Conservative here is in the sense that we&amp;rsquo;d like to have a maximize recall. Good is in the sense that we still want our classifier to have reasonable accuracy.
Results: A number of different classifiers with a number of feature engineering approaches performing at varying recall levels. The Logistic Regression model resulting from this project performs with 81 percent recall and 77 percent accuracy on the test set, and this model is deployed as a flask application on Heroku.</description></item><item><title>A Rebecca Guay Artist Classifier</title><link>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/guay_classifier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/guay_classifier/</guid><description>Some Useful links this project&amp;rsquo;s github repo The jupyter notebook for this project The python mtg sdk Scryfall api used to retrieve images A useful paper on artist identification Rebecca Guay&amp;rsquo;s Website Summary of the project Magic: The Gathering (mtg) is a collectible card game developed by Richard Garfield that can be simply summarized as &amp;ldquo;Dungeons and Dragons with Cards&amp;rdquo;. One of the great features of it is the great art that comes with it.</description></item><item><title>Get in Touch</title><link>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Want to chat? I&amp;rsquo;d love to hear what you think!
Your Name Email Address An email address is required. Message</description></item><item><title>Predicting Housing Assistance Recipients</title><link>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/fulton_era_predictor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/fulton_era_predictor/</guid><description>Goal: Develop a predictor for recipients of the Emergency Rent and Utility Assistance program in Fulton County.
Results: A logistic regression and gradient boosting classifier that are 77% and 78% accurate on the test data set, respectively, with a geographical interpretable logistic regression coefficients. A heatmap interpretation of these coefficients corresponding to the location data is also implemented through the google maps python package.
Summary The Emergency Rent and Utility Assistance (ERA) program is a program throughout the united states that assists families that are in need of emergency assistance for rent and utilities resulting from the COVID-19 pandemic.</description></item></channel></rss>