<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Projects on Home</title><link>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/</link><description>Recent content in Projects on Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Diabetes Classifier</title><link>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/diabetes_classifier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/diabetes_classifier/</guid><description>Goal: The goal of this project is to develop a good conservative diabetes classifier. Conservative here is in the sense that we&amp;rsquo;d like to have a maximize recall. Good is in the sense that we still want our classifier to have reasonable accuracy.
Results: A number of different classifiers with a number of feature engineering approaches performing at varying recall levels. The Logistic Regression model resulting from this project performs with 84 percent recall and 76 percent accuracy on the test set, and this model is deployed as a flask application on Heroku.</description></item><item><title>A Rebecca Guay Artist Classifier</title><link>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/guay_classifier/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/guay_classifier/</guid><description>Goal: The purpose for this project is twofold. Immediately, this is a curiosity project, as I wanted to see if I could use techniques I&amp;rsquo;ve learned from convolutional neural networks (CNN) not to just identify objects, but also artist styles. Second, it serves as a precursor to one day creating a neural transfer project which takes an input of art and &amp;ldquo;guayifies&amp;rdquo; it, turning it into art in the style of Rebecca Guay.</description></item><item><title>Modeling Ozone Pollution Using Linear Regression (in development)</title><link>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/ozone_linear_regression/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/ozone_linear_regression/</guid><description>Most of us probably remember learning about the protection that the ozone layer in the upper atmosphere lends us. However, ground level ozone has well documented negative effects. Those with Asthma are particularly at risk to it [1]. Denver has one of the worst levels of ground level ozone in the united states [2]. It is well known that ozone is greatly affected by pollutants emitted by cars, power plants, refineries, etc.</description></item><item><title>Predicting Housing Assistance Recipients</title><link>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/fulton_era_predictor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jcummingsutk.github.io/post/fulton_era_predictor/</guid><description>Goal: Develop a predictor for recipients of the Emergency Rent and Utility Assistance program in Fulton County.
Results: A logistic regression and gradient boosting classifier that are 77% and 78% accurate on the test data set, respectively, with geographical interpretable logistic regression coefficients. A heatmap interpretation of these coefficients corresponding to the location data is also implemented through the google maps python package.
Useful Links Check out the to see the code for the project described below.</description></item></channel></rss>